{
    "subject": "Bhumibol_Adulyadej",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Sirikit",
    "human_readable": "Bhumibol Adulyadej is married to Sirikit.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9695823192596436,
            "question": "Who is Bhumibol Adulyadej married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9473333954811096,
            "question": "Name the wife of Bhumibol Adulyadej."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8974956274032593,
            "question": "To whom was Sirikit married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8855953216552734,
            "question": "Is Sirikit married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.879275918006897,
            "question": "What is the name of Bhumibol Adulyadej's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8780083656311035,
            "question": "What type of relationship exists between Bhumibol Adulyadej and Sirikit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8676468729972839,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage of Bhumibol Adulyadej?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14071127772331238,
            "question": "Who is the king in this relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10247498750686646,
            "question": "Who is known as King Rama IX?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09401386976242065,
            "question": "What is the name of the queen in this relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bhumibol Adulyadej is married to Sirikit.",
            "html": "yago_23188_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is known as King Rama IX?",
            "html": "yago_23188_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the king in this relationship?",
            "html": "yago_23188_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the marriage of Bhumibol Adulyadej?",
            "html": "yago_23188_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23188_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23188_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23188_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23188_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23188_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23188_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23188_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23188_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23188_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23188_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide evidence that supports the triple, as they mention Queen Sirikit's marriage to King Bhumibol Adulyadej, their engagement, and their coronation together."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that King Bhumibol Adulyadej and Mom Rajawongse Sirikit Kitayakara were married on April 28, 1950. Therefore, the triple \"Bhumibol Adulyadej is married to Sirikit\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}